Manual life super visa insurance. So
manual life one of the top companies in
Canada and worldwide as well. Go to
website btown insurance.com and if you
are following this video on the phone
then click on these two lines. Click on
manual life
and uh if you want to read about manual
life super visa insurance policy read
this page. Manual life offers two plans
plan A and plan B. So, plan A without
pre-existing health conditions and uh
plan B is with the pre-existing health
conditions. Click on get your official
manual life code here. You will be
redirected to this page. Accept cookies.
Agree to the their agreement. So, right
here we have multiple insurance options.
So, first is uh traveling Canadians. It
is not for visitors. It is not for super
visa. And uh next is visitors to Canada.
So visitor to Canada is for super visa
and visitors as well. And click on get
code. On this page select do you need
insurance for super visa? Say yes and uh
then the arrival date and then the
effective date. So they should be same
effective date and arrival date. So
let's say you selected uh uh 1st April
cuz you are applying for super visa now
but later on uh you find that you're
still waiting for visa then you should
contact me before 1st April and I will
be able to update the date according to
your requirements. uh let's say you
selected 1st July but you received visa
on 1st May and your parents decided to
come to Canada on 15th May and then we
will be able to update the date again if
you contact me on uh uh before 15th May.
So my number is right there on the top
of this website and uh my name is there
as well. So minimum 100,000 as per
immigration Canada. You can go for 150
as well. And uh then uh you can select
the province. So I am licensed in
Ontario, Alberta and British Columbia.
So you can choose these provinces, one
of these provinces.
If you are [clears throat] living in any
another province, contact me. I will be
able to help you that with that as well.
So next is date of birth. This is your
parents date of birth. They are coming
together, right? Mom and dad. Then uh
click companion here. Then click on show
plans. So now it will show you plans. It
will show you two plans. So first plan
is uh plan A. The plan A price is
$1737
Canadian for the full year. Right? So
this price is with the $75
deductible. You can go for zero
deductible from here. then the price
will be 1,824
and uh this will cover like 100,000 plan
B. So plan B you have to answer a
questionnaire for the plan B price. So
plan B includes pre-existing health
condition. Click on start questionnaire
and uh then you will answer these
questions. So I will go for with the no
with all questions because mostly these
are no but uh you should read these 10
by one and uh now you will be able to
see the price of plan B this is with 75
deductible again I'm going to choose
zero deductible here and the plan B
price is $2,8
so $28 for a year for the man life and
if you want to choose another deductible
then uh let's Say you chose 1,000 then
the premium will decrease accordingly
right. So 1,530.
So a,000 deductible means that uh you
have to pay up to,000. If the bill is
let's say like $200 then uh you you
cannot claim because it's under a,000.
If the medical bill is let's say $5,000
then uh you will claim and uh they will
pay according to the policy conditions.
Click on select and uh then uh click on
this box agreement and then click on
apply. If you want to read these
eligibility questions. So these are most
common eligibility questions. Almost all
insurance providers ask these questions.
So check these questions and uh click on
uh this check box if you are confirmed
and then click on apply.
So now on this page fill up the
information again. Uh this is the first
name last name of your parent and uh
then their sets. Then uh your contact
email and uh country of uh residence.
Let's say they are coming from India.
You can fill India here, right? And uh
then your Canadian address. This should
be your Canadian address and where your
parents will be coming to meet you.
Right? and then click on continue. So
just confirm your details here. Fill the
credit card information there and then
click on purchase. If you want to read
term and condition uh terms and
conditions are at the very bottom of the
page. So this is how you buy uh manual
life super visa insurance. Contact me if
you have any question.
My WhatsApp number is right here on our
website betaon insurance.com. So you can
WhatsApp, call or email me from here for
further questions. Thank you.